Vladislav Astakhov

Junior Web Developer

A developer working with the React-Redux stack. I enjoy solving difficulties and gaining new knowledge every day. My goal is to become a Senior Full Stack Developer in 4 years. I would like to join a team of experienced programmers who make necessary and interesting projects.

Skills

- HTML5/ CSS3
- JavaScript
- React + Redux
- TypeScript
- SASS

Work history

Shift Supervisor Western Siberian Petrochemical Complex Limited Lia, Tobolsk, Tyumen state Organization of work of shift personnel, performance of complex switching in electrical installations, performance of audits of work, development of documentation.	2020-10 – Current
Operator Western Siberian Petrochemical Complex Limited Lia, Tobolsk, Tyumen state Acting as a shift supervisor, continuously monitoring the state of the enterprise's power supply scheme, setting up the logic of the automation system.	2018-03 – 2020-10

Education

Course «JavaScript Junior Frontend Developer» [Vladilen Minin]	2021
Course «CSS - The Complete Guide 2021» [Udemy]	2021
Course «React for beginners» [Udemy]	2021
Tyumen Industrial University, Tyumen State Master of Science, Power System Automation	2017-09 – 2019-07
Amur State University, Amur State Bachelor of Science, Power Stations	2013-09 – 2017-07

Contact

Address	Social Website
Tobolsk, TYU, 625000	LinkedIn:
Email Address	https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladislav-astakhov-4a2107208
astakhov.vlad.work@gmail.com	VK: https://vk.com/ast.vlad
Phone	GitHub: https://github.com/AstakhovV

89146017354